Jane Q. Fullstacker

jdoe@onecoolstartup.io 1-650-999-7777 http://janef.me/blog



Full-stack software developer with 6+ years industry experience specializing in scalable cloud architectures for this, that, and the other. A native of southern CA, Jane enjoys hiking, mystery novels, and the company of Rufus, her two-year-old beagle.





EMPLOYMENT

Head Code Ninja, One Cool Startup

2013-09-2015-12

Development team manager for OneCoolApp and OneCoolWebsite, a free social network tiddlywink generator and lifestyle portal with over 200,000 users.

Principal Developer, Veridian Dynamics

2011-07-2013-08

Developer on numerous projects culminating in technical lead role for the **Jabberwocky project** and promotion to principal developer.

IT Administrator, Stark Industries

2008-10-2011-06

Junior programmer with heavy code responsibilities. Promoted to intermediate role after 6 months.

Intern, Dunder Mifflin

2008-06-2008-09

Performed IT administration and deployments for Dunder Mifflin.



EDUCATION

Cornell University

2005-09-2008-05

Medfield College

2003-09-2005-06



SERVICE

Technical Consultant, Technology for Tots

Summary of this volunteer stint.

- Accomplishment 1
- Accomplishment 2
- etc

NCO, US Army Reserves

1999-11-2003-06

Summary of this military stint.

- Accomplishment 1
- Accomplishment 2
- etc



W PUBLICATIONS

Building User Interfaces with Electron and Atom, Code Project

Published on: 2011-01

Jane Fullstacker's Blog, self

Published on: 2011-01

Teach Yourself GORFF in 21 Days, Amazon

Published on: 2008-01



W AWARDS

Honorable Mention, Google

2012

Summa cum laude, Cornell University

2012